Guide to the Paper Tiger Television Archive, ca. 1981-2014 MSS.276
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Video recordings
  - Subseries B: PTTV - Non-broadcast Videotapes
    - Iran Tape - Map with "It's 8:30...Do You Know Where Your Brain is?" / Iran Tape - Dancing Sequence - new show, March 4, 1989 (Box 74, Media ID: 276.0318)
    - CBS News footage on Saudi Arabia (Box 74, Media ID: 276.0319)
    - This Is A Sex Ad: PTTV Reads the Catholic Bishop's PR Campaign - studio tape, May 23, 1990 (Box 74, Media ID: 276.0320)
    - Deep Dish T.V. - Getting a Grip on Access (Box 74, Media ID: 276.0321)
    - Interviews with Asians on Koreatown (CAAV) - Micyoung Cho & ? - Rodney King tape - Rony Avalos, May 21, 1992 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0322)
    - TV News L.A. Riots - tape #2 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0323)
    - News Footage on LA Riots (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0324)
    - N.Y. Street Interviews on the L.A. Rebellion, May 1, 1992 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0325)
    - News Show Shots Misc: Only first 20 or so minutes, shot by May Ying Welsh - Rodney King Beating, Channel 7 News, approx. 6 minutes - Pete Jennings at Media Demo, shot by Simone Farkhondeh, approx. 14 minutes - Anchors, onlookers & Icecubes in strobe (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0326)
    - American Liberty: L.A. Rebellion segment, 6 minutes (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0327)
    - Malcolm X demo, 7 minutes, Simone Farkondeh - Rally, demonstration United Nations - December 12 Movement - Malcolm X birthday, May 19, 1992 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0328)
    - Malcolm X Birthday, tape 1, Master, shot by: May Ying Welsh, May 1992 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0329)
    - Malcolm X Birthday, tape 2, Master, shot by: May Ying Welsh, May 1992 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0330)
    - TV News on LA Riots, tape 1 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0331)
    - Simone Watney Speaks About Clause 28 and Homophobia in the U.K., Deccember 1988 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0332)
    - Judith Williamson Consumes Pasionately in Southern California (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0333)
    - Daniel del Solar and PBS, B-camera, bump from 8mm camera original, June 30, 1989 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0334)
    - Dennis O'Neil Reads Rock N' Roll Fanzines - master 2 (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0335)
    - Michelle Mattelart - final rough cut - last 30 minutes (Box 75, Media ID: 276.0336)
    - World What World! Cranky #2, April 30, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0337)
    - Guerrilla Girls at the Clocktower/Whitney Exhibit - tape #1, May 17, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0338)
    - Vet's Speak Out #2, San Francisco - C.O.'s statement (cont. from tape #1) - Viet vet; Jesse Drew + Carle Leshne - PTTV West, February 2, 1991 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0339)
    - Guerrilla Girls Clocktower/Whitney Exhibit, tape #3, May 17, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0340)
    - 8mm bump-up of Philly stuff (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0341)
    - Guerilla Girls Whitney Exhibit at Clocktower, tape #4, May 17, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0342)
    - Philadelphia Mag, tape 1, April 11, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0343)
    - Guerrilla Girls Whitney Exhibit/Clocktower, tape 2, May 17, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0344)
    - Philadelphia Mag, tape 2, April 11, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0345)
    - Daniel Del Solar looks at PBS; A-camera; dub from Hi-8 camera master; mixed audio on 1&2; 2nd generation transfer from camera original, June 30, 1989 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0346)
    - Carlos Fernando Charmorro Reads Barricada - original (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0347)
    - Herb Schiller Smashes the Crash - master, December 9, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0348)
    - Shelia Smith-Hobson on Grenada - dub master from 2 studio/camera originals, both slightly damaged (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0349)
    - William Kunstler - Master, November 18, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0350)
    - William Kunstler - cutaways, November 18, 1987 (Box 76, Media ID: 276.0351)
    - Paper Tiger Scans The (Inter)National Audiovideo Fe$tival, October 26, 1992 / December 9, 1985 (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0523)
      Original format: 3/4" U-matic; Color; NTSC; Stereo
    - Herb Schiller Read the Times #3 - Master, November 11, 1981 (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0524)
    - Herb Schiller - Reads the NYT #6 - without inserts, December 2, 1981 (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0525)
    - Benson + Miami Vice (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0526)
    - Mumia Abu-Jamal: Giving a Face to the Death Penalty (Box 140, Media ID: 276.0527)
    - Family Feud (Box 140, Media ID: 276.0528)
    - Flo Kennedy Tapes for Middle Blackspot - Embassy Demo / Brian Winston Black Sitcom Show - Edit master - insert OT stills (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0352)
    - The Supernaturals (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0353)
    - 1. Bill Bodde Reads TV 2. From Tom + Jerry to Network TV (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0354)
    - Procter & Gamble for Soap Show - #1 (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0355)
    - Procter & Gamble for Soap Show - #2 (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0356)
    - Inserts - Ebony, TV News, Variety graphics (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0357)
    - Jack Spence & Judy Butler Read La Prensa - Dub #1 - 2 tracks - cable cast (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0358)
    - Aviation Weekly Inserts - for lenny Siegel show, January 14, 1986 (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0359)
    - Magdoff #2 (Box 77, Media ID: 276.0360)
    - Gimme a Break - Black Sitcoms (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0361)
    - Conrad Lynn Reads Commentary - with music in beginning - Wrestling (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0362)
    - Varda Bursyn on Playboy - Camera Original - first part of show - work in progress, September 1984 (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0363)
    - Tim Haight Reads Channels - tape 1 (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0364)
    - Teresa Costa Reads Biker Lifestyle - Camera Orignal - not edit (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0365)
    - Black Sitcoms (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0366)
    - Kathleen Hulser Reads Subway Ads - rough scenes - food, can-opener, plaque attack, celebrities (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0367)
    - Mary's Rock Video - Joe Q from Beta (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0368)
    - Grenada Slides - Michelle Gibbs - Bronx paster-up / Brian Winston News Selects, March 16, 1983 (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0369)
    - Michele Gibbs - #1, September 24, 1983 (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0370)
    - Michele Gibbs - #2, September 24, 1983 (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0371)
    - Subway Moive - Brock Peters, et al. - Molly channels title (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0372)
    - Myrna Bain Reads Ebony - 2nd Master - not corrected (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0373)
    - Business Week Show #1 - titles & credits (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0374)
    - Patrick Esmonde-White - Camera original #1 (Box 78, Media ID: 276.0375)
    - N.Y.S.C.A. Smapler 1991 (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0376)
    - Sampler 1994 - Rockefeller Foundation Documentary Fellowship (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0377)
    - Special Sampler for PTTV Benefit Party - Its Always the Year of the Tiger HEre, June 18, 1999 (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0378)
    - Sampler: Donna Haraway on National Geographic; Brian Winston on TV News; Thulani Davis Asks Why Howard Beach?; Judith Williamson on Sock Ads; Herb Schiller on New Technologies; Joan Does Dynasty; - Incomplete, tape ends before.... (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0379)
    - Urban Visionaries - My World - Journeys - Cips #3; The Urban Legend of Huntington Horros #4; One Family #1; Clay Life #5; Trouble #7; The Amazing Life of Scott Tsang #3; Holla Back Dubai #4, 2003 (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0380)
      Original format: 3/4" U-matic dubs from MiniDV
    - Sampler S 12 B - Harraway on Primates; Winston on TV News; Bowser on Early Black Cinema; Williamson on Southern California (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0381)
    - PTTV Bites - Sampler - Judith Williamson; Thulani David - Howard Beach; Fred Landis - Selecciones; Jill Macoska - Science Mags, 1987 (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0382)
    - Sampler #4 - Commentary; Computer Mags; Business Week; Vogue; Wokring Woman; Foreign Policy; National Enquirer; TV News; Cosmo; NY Post; Ebony (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0383)
    - Sampler - Life; Variety; Pravda (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0384)
    - Sampler - dub - Conrad Lynn, August 1983 (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0385)
    - Benton/FIVF Sampler - Rosler on Baby M; Sanbanmatsu on Animals in Media; The Weekly Mail; Ward on Tompkins Square; Silvermanan TV Without Borders, 1989 (Box 79, Media ID: 276.0386)
    - Sampler #3 - starts with Conrad Lynn, June 1983 (Box 141, Media ID: 276.0387)
    - NYSCA Sampler - Braderman; Schiller; Rosler; Winston; Tajima; Williamson / Tape label: Alex Cockburn Reads The Washington Post, 1990 (Box 141, Media ID: 276.0388)
    - NYSCA Sampler - Johns Walden, Ted Koppel; Transformer/AIDS; Page Du Bois Reads Plato; Trash TV - Herb S.; TV Across Borders; How History Was Wounded; Glamour, Terry Odendahl; Fundamentalist Feg Leaf Censorship, 1989 (Box 141, Media ID: 276.0389)
    - Sampler - Dub, August, 1983 (Box 141, Media ID: 276.0390)
    - Sampler - 87A, S4, Nysca 1987 (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0391)
    - Soc. Sch. Conference - Crisis in Kosovo - part 2 - Q & A, April, 1999 (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0392)
    - Soc. Sch. Conference - Crisis in Kosovo - part 2 - Q & A - Aleander Burgalin, Omar Dahbour, Mathew Ally, Kam Eshy (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0393)
    - IAC Demo and Interview footage, April 1999 (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0394)
    - Not Top Gun - Chip Lord - Dubbing Master, 1987 (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0395)
    - Chiapas Media Project - studio shoot - (left) Francisco Vacquec; (right) Hermenegildo Rojas with Alex; @ MNN, June 2, 1998 (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0396)
    - Video Dial Tone / George Stoney - transfer from Hi-8, September 27, 1992 (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0397)
    - On Container: Kelly Anderson, Neil Lazarus and Catherine Saafiled read The Weekly Mail / On Tape: Ellen Ray and Bill Schaap Read Covert Action Information Bulletin on State Terrorism. (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0398)
    - Processed World: The Magazine with Bad Attitude - Processed World Reads Processed World (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0399)
    - Rage in Harlem / Paper Tiger Count & Open (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0400)
      Original format: Betacam SP S
    - Patrick Esmond White On TV Coverage of Mass Demonstrations / Tompkins Square Park: Operation Class War on the Lower East Side (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0401)
    - Bicentennial (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0402)
      Original format: Betacam
    - Paper Tiger Dream House - Installation at the Wexner Center in Columbus, OH. Documentation, August 1991 - January 1992 (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0403)
    - Seventeen (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0404)
    - Jim Kavanagh Discusses Fighting Brothers: Black/White Unity in Popular American Culture (Box 80, Media ID: 276.0405)
    - Grenada #1 - Studio/Camera original B - Ending damaged - last 2 mintues with insert (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0406)
    - PSA Street Interviews 3 - Master, December 18, 1989 (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0407)
    - Grenada #1 - Studio/Camera orignial A - reinsert beginning - end damaged (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0408)
    - Two Party System - produced by PTTV for the Philly IMC - Dub Master - Master is on DV (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0409)
    - Bringing Globalism Home - Excerpts from Showdown in Seattle + Breaking the Bank (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0410)
    - 20 minute edit of "Showdown" + "Breaking Bank" for Margaret Mead Festival - Rough Edit / Media Mogul Tour - Crandi's footage (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0411)
    - Sin Sin Naughty / WKRP in Cincinnati (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0412)
    - Steal This Radio (Telecom Show) - Master (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0413)
    - Breaking the Bank - Selects from shows one and two - 30 min select cut for screenings (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0414)
    - #55 Renee Tajima Reads Asian Images / #4 Herb Schiller Reads The NYT #4 - Hanging Out in Foreign Capitals, September 21, 1991 (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0415)
    - Indymedia Newsreel #2 (Box 81, Media ID: 276.0416)
    - Source G.C., May 25, 1999 (Box 139, Media ID: 276.0417)
    - Excerpts for Open Center Screening 1. Showdown in Seattle (Big Noise) 2. Breaking the Bank (PTTV/HAVC) 3. Melbourne Rising (SKA TV) 4. Not My President (IMC NYC) 5. Chiapas 12/31/2000 (Big Noise), March 15, 2001 (Box 139, Media ID: 276.0418)
    - Deep Dish TV - The Lannan Foundation Presents "Writers Uncensored" Part 1: Allen Ginsberg - Doesn't Everybody Want to Save the World?, 1991 (Box 139, Media ID: 276.0419)
    - Offline, 1997 (Box 139, Media ID: 276.0420)
      Original format: S-VHS
    - ABC Survives, 5th Street Buried Alive (Box 139, Media ID: 276.0421)
    - Showdown in Seattle Compliation - www.indymedia.org (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0422)
    - Showdown in Seattle - Whispered Media (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0423)
    - Open Center Screening Tape - IMC Video, 1999-2000 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0424)
    - Open Center Screening Tape - IMC Video 1999-2000 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0425)
    - Post LA Riot interviews in NYC Streets, May 1, 1992 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0426)
    - Crashing the Party, Part 2 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0427)
    - Crashing the Party, Part 2 - office copy (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0428)
    - Crashing the Party, Part 1 - office copy (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0429)
    - Crashing the Party: RNC, August 1, 2000 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0430)
    - Crashing the Party: RNC, August 1, 2000 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0431)
    - Crashing the Party: RNC, August 3, 2000 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0432)
    - Crashing the Party: RNC, July 31, 2000 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0433)
    - Crashing the Party: RNC, July 31, 2000 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0434)
    - Crashing the Party, Part 2 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0435)
    - Interviews with Weston & Jnol (?), November 3 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0436)
      Original format: MiniDV
    - 096 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0437)
    - Noon Rally, tape 1, Sasa & Josh - Street Interviews, December 3 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0438)
    - Ken Koenig / Makin' Clubs (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0439)
    - 760 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0440)
    - Herb Schiller, March 1991 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0441)
      Original format: Hi-8
    - Cyberspace Workshop (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0442)
    - Sam Anderson: The Gulf War & the Renewed Rise of Racism - Discussion - Learning Alliance (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0443)
    - Telecom - Internet Cafe & Cybercafe / Paul Kneisel / B-roll (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0444)
    - Riverfront and May Day Fest (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0445)
    - Global Show - interview with Kyla Slaven, Sydney Australia - master (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0446)
    - Denise + Tara - Sin Sin Naughty - Workshop Trip (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0447)
    - Media & Decmocracy Conference - Evening session / Media Moguls Protest, October 16, 1997 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0448)
    - Media & Decmocracy Conference - Thursday Evening / Hightower, October 16, 1997 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0449)
    - Burlington Workshop (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0450)
    - Rome's tape - DC workshop (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0451)
    - Burn The Mayor, July 28, 1999 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0452)
    - Showdown in Seattle - Hour-long compilation final edit master, January 1, 2000 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0453)
      Original format: DVCam
    - Williamsburgh Bridge Demo Anti-Incinerator demo + march (when Dinkins was Mayor) - Interviews, early 1990s (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0454)
    - International Series Sampler (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0456)
    - Telecom - master, June 1996 (Box 82, Media ID: 276.0457)
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous Videotapes
    - TPTV Compilation - a Global Action Production (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0458)
    - Dolls and Dust - Thailand/HK, 1998 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0459)
      Original format: VHS; NTSC; Audio on RCA not RF
    - TV Viva - Brazil (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0460)
    - Who's Taking Over? World Trade Organization, Seattle, 1999 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0461)
    - Mining the Land of Cain: The Innu vs Inco at Voisey's Bay (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0462)
    - Gallery TV - Brazil, 1997 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0463)
    - Nuyorican Dream - HRWIFF, 2000 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0464)
    - Nebbish - an Andy Andrew film, 2000 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0465)
    - TV Plus! #7, 2003 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0466)
    - The Trickle Down Theory of Sorrow, part 1 - Safe at Home (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0467)
    - One Family - Global Action Project (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0468)
    - Holler (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0469)
    - Maxinbomba TV / Interview with Dee Dee (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0470)
    - Remembering the American Farm: Scenes from Howell Farm Living History Museum (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0471)
    - W-TV Office / Yutaka Tsuchiya - Master (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0472)
    - Without Television, volume 001-003/ Yutaka Tsuchiya - Master (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0473)
    - DC Youth - transferred footage (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0474)
    - Green Chimneys / what is this? (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0475)
    - DC Youth - transferred footage (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0476)
    - A Good Kill - dailies, day 6, for Greg Tilson, September 28, 1992 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0477)
    - Green Chimney - Tampon Commercial (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0478)
    - Green Chimneys Deconstruct Commercials (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0479)
    - Human Rights: 10 Years in 10 Minutes - Chuck Scott (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0480)
    - America's Least Wanted / C + OK (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0481)
    - Dissent in RGB - Dee Dee (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0482)
    - Rhythm and Rights: Radio Station Lok'shini FM, South Africa - a dramatic 13-part series - NTSC dub tape 2 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0483)
    - Columbian video 1. Yo'upkku .... illegible (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0484)
    - Global Show Interviews 1. Videoazimut 2. Kyla Slaven (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0485)
    - Dreams, Desires, Lunacies (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0486)
    - Rhythm and Rights: Radio Station Lok'shini FM, South Africa - a dramatic 13-part series - NTSC dub tape 1 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0487)
    - TV (Espera) Sala de Espera / Brasil - A Sampler Shot - about cooperatives in the town for cheaper food... (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0488)
    - Document Karoshi (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0489)
    - Okinawa's Anti-war Landownders (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0490)
    - Waiting Room TV (Brazil) - in Portugese (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0491)
    - Korean Labor Movement: 1987-1995 (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0492)
    - Video Press - sample of our media - Tokyo, Japan (Box 83, Media ID: 276.0493)
    - Da Zanza A Marcha Da Luta A Terra (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0494)
    - Unicamp sampler, 1996 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0495)
    - Pela Trilha De Arquimedes (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0496)
    - Radio Novelas, 1994 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0497)
    - Identity? / What Do You Think About the Was Responsibility of Emperor Hirohito?, August 15 1996 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0498)
    - Identity? / What Do You Think About the Was Responsibility of Emperor Hirohito? (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0499)
    - Blood and Sweat of Migrant Workers in China (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0500)
    - Dongguan Fire, 1991 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0501)
    - TV Pinel (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0502)
    - Historia de Pescador - Um video educativo sobre pesca predatoria (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0503)
    - Withdraw U.S. Bases! Appeal From Okinawa (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0504)
    - ZTV: Resistance Through Communication - Zapatista (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0505)
    - Democracy Now! Democratic National Convention - 1 hour compilation - edit master (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0506)
    - Democracy Now! LA Democratic National Convention - part one of compilation (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0507)
    - Democracy Now! Democratic National Convention - part 2 compilation - 2nd 1/2 hour (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0508)
    - Democracy Now! LA - control track break approximately 16 min (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0509)
    - Sunrise Over Tiananmen Square / Democracy Now! Philladelphia Republican National Convention 2000 - part 1 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0510)
    - Democracy Now! LA, August 18 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0511)
    - Democracy Now! LA - Wednesday, August 16 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0512)
    - Democracy Now! LA - Tuesday, August 15 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0513)
    - Saude Mitos & Verdades - Stress E Coracao, August 1997 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0514)
    - La Matanza de Aquas Blancas / Marcos (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0515)
    - Vagrom - tape 1 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0516)
    - Encuentro Feminista Latinoamericano y del Caribe - Tejiendo Rebeldias (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0517)
    - Democracy Now! LA - Democractic National Convention 2000 - 1 hour compilation (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0518)
    - Democracy Now! Woman With Black Eye / Live Broadcast (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0519)
    - Democracy Now! LA Democractic National Convention 2000 - 1 hour compilation (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0520)
    - Democracy Now! Breaking With Convention - Broadcast second hour - copy from Master DVCam, August 17, 2000 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0521)
    - Democracy Now! Breaking With Convention - Broadcast first hour - copy from Master DVCam, August 17, 2000 (Box 84, Media ID: 276.0522)
- Series IX: Objects (Oversize)
  This series contains the objects created by Paper Tiger TV, which were used as props for their programming and installations. It also includes "crankees" (hand-painted scrolls used to display credits in videos) and backdrops. The crankees are listed by show number. To see a list of Paper Tiger TV shows, go to PaperTiger.org or look at one of the paper catalogs in the Publicity series.
  - Subseries A: Props
    - Banner with political buttons, Undated (Box 40, Object ID: 276.2.0001)
    - Denim jacket with crankee on the back, Undated (Box 42, Object ID: 276.2.0002)
    - Felt cloth with tigers, Undated (Box 41, Object ID: 276.2.0016)
    - Framed National Geographic cover - painted, Undated (Box 41, Object ID: 276.2.0003)
    - Framed photograph of Herb Schiller with wire on glass, Undated (Box 41, Object ID: 276.2.0004)
    - Grey "TV" box - large, Undated; 1 item one box (Object ID: 276.2.0005)
      Props (object genres)
    - Grey "TV" box - small, Undated; 1 item one box (Object ID: 276.2.0006)
    - Large wooden prop TV remote control - blue, Undated (Box 41, Object ID: 276.2.0007)
    - Large wooden prop TV remote control - pink, Undated (Box 41, Object ID: 276.2.0008)
    - Operation Storm the Media - camcorder commando vests (2), Undated (Box 41, Object ID: 276.2.0015)
    - Paper Tiger TV logo - in black picture frame, Undated (Box 40, Object ID: 276.2.0009)
    - Plastic hook hand, Undated (Box 41, Object ID: 276.2.0010)
    - Political buttons, Undated (Box 40, Object ID: 276.2.0011)
    - Shrinky-dink pins, earrings, and magnets, Undated (Box 40, Object ID: 276.2.0012)
    - Tiger stripe box (red and black) with slit cut in lid, Undated; 1 item one box (Object ID: 276.2.0013)
    - Toy phone - yellow plastic, Undated (Box 40, Object ID: 276.2.0014)
  - Subseries B: Crankees
    Subseries B is comprised of "crankees"--hand-painted scrolls used to display credits in videos. The crankees are listed by show number. To see a list of Paper Tiger TV shows, go to PaperTiger.org or look at one of the paper catalogs in the Publicity series.
    - Show # 13, 1982 (Box 44, Object ID: 276.2.0044)
    - Show # 13, 1982 (Box 45, Object ID: 276.2.0070)
    - Show # 15, 1982 (Box 43, Object ID: 276.2.0030)
    - Show # 18, 1982 (Box 43, Object ID: 276.2.0034)
    - Show # 22, 1983 (Box 45, Object ID: 276.2.0074)
    - Show # 23, 1982 (Box 45, Object ID: 276.2.0075)
    - Show # 27, 1983 (Box 43, Object ID: 276.2.0029)
    - Show # 30, 1983 (Box 44, Object ID: 276.2.0049)
    - Show # 33, 1982 (Box 43, Object ID: 276.2.0031)
    - Show # 38, 1983 (Box 43, Object ID: 276.2.0032)
    - Show # 40, 1983 (Box 45, Object ID: 276.2.0071)
    - Show # 41, 1983 (Box 44, Object ID: 276.2.0047)
    - Show # 42, 1983 (Box 43, Object ID: 276.2.0033)
    - Show # 43, 1983 (Box 44, Object ID: 276.2.0041)
    - Show # 56, 1984 (Box 44, Object ID: 276.2.0039)
    - Show # 57, 1984 (Box 43, Object ID: 276.2.0035)
    - Show # 58, 1984 (Box 43, Object ID: 276.2.0023)
    - Show # 65, 1985 (Box 44, Object ID: 276.2.0045)
    - Show # 70, 1985 (Box 44, Object ID: 276.2.0048)
    - Show # 70, 1985 (Box 45, Object ID: 276.2.0073)